[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Did actor Al Pacino turn down the lead role in the film Pretty Woman?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What other name is commonly used for the Japanese Macaque, a monkey native to Japan?", "correct_answer": "Snow Monkey", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Whistling Monkey", "Storm Monkey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mercury is the densest major body in the solar system.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which of the following areas are cacti used?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Building / construction", "Cooking", "Medicine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Yellow Sea is connected to what ocean?", "correct_answer": "Pacific", "incorrect_answers": ["Atlantic", "Arctic", "Indian"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Young Frankenstein, how does Frederick lure the monster back to the castle?", "correct_answer": "He plays music", "incorrect_answers": ["He chases him back into the castle.", "He entices him with food.", "He has Elizabeth call him."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which term refers to the cephalic disorder, characterised by absence of the celebral hemispheres?", "correct_answer": "hydranencephaly", "incorrect_answers": ["ethmocephaly", "lissercephaly", "anencephaly"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which character in the film Operation Petticoat uses her girdle to fix part of the machinery?", "correct_answer": "Maj. Edna Haywood, RN", "incorrect_answers": ["Lt. Dolores Crandall, RN", "Lt. Barbara Duran, RN", "Lt. Watson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The former prison island of Alcatraz, situated off the coast of San Francisco, is said to be the home to a number of ghosts of prisoners who died there.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is not a fluid?", "correct_answer": "All of these are fluids.", "incorrect_answers": ["Air", "Oil", "Helium"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How do mermaids enchant people according to legends and myths?", "correct_answer": "By singing", "incorrect_answers": ["By sprinkling them with magic powder", "By dancing", "With their eyes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the Vegas casino security man who has his eye on the team and especially on Ben in the movie 21?", "correct_answer": "Cole Williams", "incorrect_answers": ["Randy Peters", "Jason Little", "Mathew Mathews"]}]